https://www.high-voltage.com/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement
This web site is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement is intended to describe how your personal information is processed and used, and we will make every effort to ensure that our activities keep within the spirit of this Privacy Statement. Please note that by visiting and using this web site, or any other web site owned and operated by this web site owner, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement and all terms and conditions within our Legal Notice.
What Information is this web site gathering about its visitors and how is it being used?
Every computer connected to the Web is provided with a domain name (e.g. someispname.com) and an IP Address (e.g. 192.164.13.145). When a visitor requests a page from within this web site, our Web Servers automatically identify and log the HTTP request that is made to our Web Server. By itself, this information reveals nothing personal about you. The information that we usually gather and create a log of is as follows:
• The IP Address of the Site that may have Referred you.
• Your IP Address
• The Web Page that you may have linked to us from if any.
• The Product Identifier for Version and Make of Browser (e.g. Web Explorer®)
• The Operating System platform that you may be running (e.g. Macintosh® or Windows®)
• Search Words or Terms that are passed from a Search Engine (e.g. Google® or Yahoo!®)
• Information readily available and stored in your Adobe® Flash System.Capabilities Object.
There is absolutely nothing special about the information just described, and the practice of collecting this data has been generally standardized by most Web Servers and sites on the Web today.
The purpose of this information is actually two-fold. One, this web site has found it advantageous to examine visitor traffic in its aggregate, so that we can ensure maximum support and compatibility for the various Browsers and Operating Systems that visit our site. Additionally, as any business should attest, it is our desire to generate greater amounts of visitor traffic. By analyzing visitation patterns, referring URLs and Search Engine terms, we can strategically enhance our exposure on the Web.
What about Cookies?
Cookies are small pieces of data that are transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser from a Web Server. A cookie cannot read data from your hard disk or read cookie files that may have been created from other sites. This web site may utilize cookies as a means of providing personalization features to our visitors. For example, we may utilize cookies as a convenience to remember settings (music preferences, colors, language settings, etc.) that you may have made at our web site.
You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. Typically, by accessing the browser’s help feature you can obtain information on how to prevent your browser from accepting all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience on our web site and other websites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended. We generally give notice when cookies are required.
What other information does this web site request?
We may request your e-mail address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a survey, adding you to our mailing list, or by your request to have someone contact you for additional information. Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. We maintain a strict, No Spam or UCE, a policy which means we do not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent.
In addition, this web site will not send you e-mail that you have not agreed to receive. If you are a member of our Mailing List, you will be contacted with announcements, news, portfolio additions, and new products or services. You have the option of Unsubscribing from our Mailing List at any time, thereby disabling any further such e-mail communication from being sent to you. If you wish to have specific communications with a member of this web site staff, you will be required to provide specific information that will be routed to the appropriate contact within this web site.
What information does this web site collect when I purchase something?
If you purchase something, such as a T-Shirt, for example, we need to obtain the appropriate information in order to complete the transaction. Depending upon the method of payment that you select and your location, the required information may vary. However, generally speaking, we will need specific information to protectively process such transactions. We generally use features that safeguard this information by using industry standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encrypted servers. SSL encodes the information transferred between you and the server, rendering it unreadable to anyone trying to intercept the relay of that information.
Will this web site disclose the information collected to Third Parties?
This web site will only disclose your personal information or any of its log file information when required by Law or in the good-faith belief that such actions are necessary to:
• Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on this web site.
• Protect and defend the rights or property of this web site, or visitors of this web site.
• Identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the rights of third parties.
• Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.
This web site uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. This web site reserves the right to transfer information in connection with the sale of all or part of this web site capital stock or assets to any third party. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. This web site also provides links to a wide variety of other websites on the Web. We are not responsible for their Privacy Statements or how those web sites manage information about their users. We strongly urge you to check with those websites to determine their terms and conditions.
Any changes to this Privacy Statement will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. This web site reserves the right to change the terms, conditions, and notices at any time, and such modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting of such changes. You are therefore responsible for regularly reviewing this document and additional terms or notices posted on this web site. Your continued access of this web site shall be deemed your conclusive acceptance of any modified agreement.
